James D. Kim

Los Angeles/Orange County
CELL (909) 342-0400
E-MAIL bronze10000@gmail.com
MY WEBSITE

PROFILE

As a full-stack web developer with a background in research, I bring my love of learning and an analytical mindset honed from conducting experiments on a lab bench. My ultimate goal to write awesome code as I continually improve my craft as a web developer.

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive

General Assembly

1933 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, CA 90007

B.S. in Botany

University of California, Davis 1 Shields Ave, Davis, CA 95616

SKILLS

HTML & CSS Javascript Ruby on Rails Bootstrap JQuery Git SEO Shopify

Ruby MongoDB ZenCart

Liquid **PostgresSQL** Wordpress

EXPERIENCE

Contract web developer at The Joy Factory

November, 2016-currently

- Heavily modify company Shopify website (Liquid, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS)
- Modify company microsite (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence

Freelance web developer

since April, 2014

- Develop Wordpress websites
- Develop Zencart websites
- Develop Shopify websites

Tutor

Spring, **2015**

- Teach bioinformatics
- Explain current research in caloric restriction of yeast
- Use R Packages to conduct bioinformatics research using available datasets

Researcher

Spring, 2012-2014

Studied role of Ecdysone Receptor, isoform A, in Aedes aegypti mosquito

Research Specialist

2005-2012(Spring)

Studied G-protein signaling in filamentous fungus, Neurospora crassa

Research Associate

1994-2002

Plant Pathology department of Seminis Vegetable Seeds, Co.

Available upon request

REFERENCES